A Finding Aid to the Museum of Craft and Folk Art Records, 1970-2012, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1976-2012; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 22.7 Linear feet Boxes 1-24; 12.14 Gigabytes ER03-ER50
  - Metamorphosis: Recycling in High Fashion (1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Models in the Mind: African Prototypes in American Patchwork (1994), 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER04. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Models in the Mind: African Prototypes in American Patchwork, Digital Documents, 1993; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes Two computer files (Folder ER04)
  - The Paintings of Kyra Nijinsky Markevitch (1994), 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Puppets and Poetry (1994), 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10-13)
  - Riches to Rags: Recycling in Japanese Rural Weaving (1994), 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Russian Lacquer Art: Pavel and Natasha Tikhomirov (1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Bacchus' Vessels (1995), 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 16-18)
  - Botswana Live: Contemporary Arts and Crafts (1995), 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videocassette (VHS). (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Edith Heath: 50 Years of Design (1995), 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Land of Morning: Treasures of the Philippines (1995), 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videocassette (VHS). (Box 12, Folder 4-7)
  - Otto and Vivika Heino: Master Potters (1995), 1990-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
  - The Saami: People of the Sun and Wind (1995), 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER05. (Box 12, Folder 10-11)
  - The Saami: People of the Sun and Wind, Digital Documents, 1995; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes Five computer files (Folder ER05)
  - Two Guatemalan Folk Painters: Lorenzo Gonzalez Chavajay and Victor Vasquez Temo (1995), 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Working Folk (1995), Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videocassette (VHS). (Box 12, Folder 13-15)
  - Circus Collages of C. T. McClusky (1996), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Craft at Gump's: The Helen Heninger Years (1996), 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Craft at Gump's: The Helen Heninger Years (1996), 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
  - Have Birdcage, Hat Box and Silk Case: Will Travel (1996), 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Jay Lewis: Found Civilization (1996), 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Pani & Fili: Breads and Threads from Italy (1996), 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videocassette (VHS). (Box 13, Folder 6-10)
  - Poe Dismuke: From Vaudeville to Carnival (1996), 1989-1996; Archival Resource Key; Includes 4 videocassettes (VHS) and 1 videocassette (Video 8). (Box 13, Folder 11-13)
  - Small Wonder (1996), 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Small Wonder (1996), 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Vitalijus Cepkauskas (1996), 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Beatrice Wood: The Lustre of 104 (1997), 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Earth and Air (1997), 1993-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
  - Ed Trinkkeller: Gentleman of Iron (1997), 1992-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Ethiopian Folk Art: The Leavitt Collection (1997), 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 7-9)
  - MetalSpeaks: The Unexpected (1997), Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - Exhibition Information and Loan Forms, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Artist Submissions, 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 11-15)
  - Peruvian Retablos: The Social and Political Art of Nicario Jimenez (1997), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 16-17)
  - Sha Sha Higby (1997), 1995-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 18-19)
  - Sha Sha Higby (1997), 1996; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Sticks (1997), 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Navajo Folk Art (1997-1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
  - Straw Trails: An Exhibition of Art in Straw (1997-1998), 1992-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
  - Bert Marsh: British Woodturner (1998), 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
  - British Potters: The Dixon Long Collection (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Face to Face: Portraits by Craig Budde and Ted Gordon (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Ted Gordon, Artwork Labels, Digital Document, 1998; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER06)
  - Five Points of View: Baskets by Contemporary Artists (1998), 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 11-14)
  - Folk Art of Bali (1998), 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - June Schwarcz: Forty Years/Forty Pieces (1998), 1996-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 16-19)
  - June Schwarcz: Forty Years/Forty Pieces (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 16)
    - General Exhibition Information, 1981-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Documentary, 1989; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (U-matic) Master; 2 Videocassettes (VHS) Subbed version and extra footage; 1 Videocassettes (U-matic) Dubbed version; 3 Videocassettes (VHS) Looped version and duplicates; 2 Videocassettes (VHS) Looped versions (Box 16, Folder 2-6)
  - Tea Bowl Invitational (1998), 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
  - Ware for Chanoyu: The Japanese Tea Ceremony (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 9-10)
  - Ware for Chanoyu: The Japanese Tea Ceremony, Digital Documents, 1998; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes Two computer files (Folder ER07)
  - The Christmas Creche (1998-1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - The Christmas Creche, Digital Document, 1998; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER08)
  - Pat Hickman: Through the Gates (1998-1999), 1994-1999; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videocassette (VHS). (Box 16, Folder 12-13)
  - Pat Hickman, Artist Introduction, Digital Document, 1998; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER09)
  - The Delights of Brazil: Popular Art Today (1999), 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Fiber Eloquence: African Traditions (1999), 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
  - Illumination! Artists Working with Light (1999), 1993-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
  - Master in Wood: The Furniture of Art Carpenter (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Metal Arts from the Saxe Collection (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 7-9)
  - Open and Shut Cases: Boxes by Jeffrey Ketcham and Larry Jeffers (1999), 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Recycled Riches, Recycles Dreams: The Altars of Pierrot Barra (1999), 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Sacred Markers: Funerary Sculpture (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 12-14)
  - Beyond the Obvious: Rethinking Jewelry (1999-2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Rebecca Didomenico: Found Glass (1999-2000), 1995-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Chinese Children's Hats from the Qing Dynasty (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Contemporary Craft Perspectives or Craft Showcase 1 (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 18)
    There is 1 videocassette (VHS) in the Dorothy Weiss exhibition files that includes footage from this show.
  - Daily News: Newspaper Art of Gugger Peter (2000), 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Death and Memory: Mexico's Dia de los Muertos (2000), 1997-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Et Cetera: Metalwork of Jack Chandler (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Florence Resnikoff: Master of Metal (2000), 1998-200; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - An Intimate Reading: The Books of Kay Sekimachi (2000), 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Jean Williams Cacicedo: Explorations in Cloth (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Papua New Guinea: Spirit and Artifacts (2000), 1985-2000; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER10. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Papua New Guinea: Spirit and Artifacts, Digital Document, 2000; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER10)
  - Reliquaries for America (2000), 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
  - A Tribute to Dorothy Weiss: Contemporary Ceramics (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - A Tribute to Dorothy Weiss: Contemporary Ceramics (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Includes 2 videocassettes (VHS), 1 of which also contains footage from Contemporary Craft Perspectives (2000).
  - Bob Stocksdale: Eighty-Eight Turnings (2001), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Contemporary Needlework: Tattoo! (2001), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 videocassettes (VHS). (Box 18, Folder 11-12)
  - Craft Showcase 2 (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 13-14)
  - Crowning Glory: Contemporary Paper Hats by Moses (2001), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER11. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Crowning Glory: Contemporary Paper Hats by Moses, Digital Documents, 2001; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes Three computer files (Folder ER11)
  - Larry Williamson: The West in Wood (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 16-17)
  - Rio Grande Traditions in Fiber and Clay (2001), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videocassette (VHS). (Box 18, Folder 18-19)
  - Shibori Tradition and Innovation: From East to West (2001), Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER12. (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
  - Shibori Tradition and Innovation: From East to West, Digital Photographs, 2001; Archival Resource Key; 0.061 Gigabytes 14 computer files (Folder ER12)
  - Craft Showcase 3 (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Emblems of Passage: Art of Africa, Oceania, and The Americas (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - General Exhibition Information, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 6-9)
    - Photograph Album of Opening, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - "Program Services - Bay Area People", 2002; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Findings: The Jewelry of Ramona Solberg (2002), 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videocassette (VHS). (Box 19, Folder 12-13)
  - Fusing Traditions: Transformations in Glass by Native American Artists (2002), 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 videocassettes (VHS). (Box 19, Folder 14-15)
  - Sirens and Snakes: Water Spirits in Folk Art and Legend (2002), 1999-2003; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videocassette (VHS) and born digital records, see ER13. (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
  - Sirens and Snakes: Water Spirits in Folk Art and Legend, Digital Photographs, 2002; Archival Resource Key; 0.318 Gigabytes Eight computer files (Folder ER13)
  - Unwearable Art: Clothing in New Media (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
  - Bella Feldman: War Toys Redux (2003), 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
  - Craft Showcase 4 (2003), Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Quilted Journeys: Immigration Stories by Australian Artists (2003), 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Revealing Influences: Conversations with Bay Area Artists (2003), Archival Resource Key (Box 20)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Financial Records, Loan Forms, and Research, 2001-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Research, 2001-2004; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER14. (Box 20, Folder 11-12)
    - Digital Photographs, 2003; Archival Resource Key; 0.187 Gigabytes 35 computer files (Folder ER14)
    - Printed Material, 2001-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Valuables: Jewelry in the New Millenium (2003), 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 14-16)
  - Craft Showcase 5 (2004), Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - The New Rice Festival: Vietnamese Artist Nguyen Bao Toan (2004), Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER15. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - The New Rice Festival: Vietnamese Artist Nguyen Bao Toan, Digital Photographs, 2000, 2003; Archival Resource Key; 0.038 Gigabytes 38 computer files (Folder ER15)
  - New Urushi Forms: Three Lacquer Artists from Japan (2004), Archival Resource Key (Box 21)
    - Correspondence, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Contracts, Financial Records, Loan Forms and Research, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Press Materials, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Exhibition Visuals, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Photographic Material, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Ragged Beauty: Repaired Textiles and Other Objects (2004), 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Ragged Beauty: Repaired Textiles and Other Objects (2004), 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Ragged Beauty: Repaired Textiles and Other Objects (2004), 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER16. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - The Roving Tailor, video by Daniel Gorrell (2004), Digital Video Recording, 2019; Archival Resource Key; 0.376 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER16)
  - Subtraction and Addition: Ceramic Sculpture and Installations (2004), Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 11-12)
  - Weaving Tradition: Carol Cassidy and Woven Silks of Laos (2004), 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videocassette (VHS) and born digital records, see ER17. (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
  - Weaving Tradition: Carol Cassidy and Woven Silks of Laos, Digital Photographs and Documents, 2003; Archival Resource Key; 0.023 Gigabytes 64 computer files (Folder ER17)
  - Material Masters: Craft Exhibition (2005), Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Mithila Paintings: The Evolution of an Art Form (2005), 2004-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Sanctuary in an Age of Commodity: The Art of Tobi Kahn (2005), 2003-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Folk Art for the Soul from Bay Area Collections (2005-2006), Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Sensuous Curves: Scandinavian Designs Then and Now (2006), Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER18. (Box 21, Folder 19-20)
  - Sensuous Curves: Scandinavian Designs Then and Now, Digital Photographs, 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key; 1.71 Gigabytes 78 computer files (Folder ER18)
  - Will the Circle be Unbroken: Four Generations of African-American Quiltmakers (2006), Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - The Art of Gaman: Arts and Crafts from the Japanese American Internment Camps, 1942-1946 (2006-2007), Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - The Art of Gaman: Arts and Crafts from the Japanese American Internment Camps, 1942-1946, Digital Document, 2006; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER19)
  - Beats Per Minute: Contemporary Artists Influenced by Craft and Folk Art Practices (2007), 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER20. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Julio Cesar Morales, Digital Photographs and Documents, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.012 Gigabytes 37 computer files (Folder ER20)
  - Beyond Craft: Kamisuki, Paper as Process (2007), 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER21. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Haigyu, Digital Presentation, 2006; Archival Resource Key; 0.141 Gigabytes ER21 (Folder ER21)
  - Evolution of the Ukelele: The Story of Hawaii's Jumping Flea (2007), 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER22-ER25. (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
  - Legends of Ukulele, Digital Audio Recording, 1998; Archival Resource Key; 0.483 Gigabytes 18 computer files (Folder ER22)
  - Evolution of the Ukulele: The Story of Hawaii's Jumping Flea, Curator Tour, Digital Video Recording, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.831 Gigabytes 37 computer files (Folder ER23)
  - Evolution of the Ukulele: The Story of Hawaii's Jumping Flea, Concert on August 19, 2007, Digital Photographs and Video Recordings, Archival Resource Key; 0.274 Gigabytes 40 computer files (Folder ER24)
  - Ukuleles in Paradise, Digital Audio Recording, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.448 Gigabytes 10 computer files (Folder ER25)
  - "C" Change, Craft in Our Future (2007-2008), Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER26-ER27. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - "C" Change, Craft in Our Future, Curator Tour and Reception, Digital Photographs and Video Recordings, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.884 Gigabytes 43 computer files (Folder ER26)
  - "C" Change, Craft in Our Future, Digital Documents and Photographs, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.144 Gigabytes 114 computer files (Folder ER27)
  - American Symbols: From Lady Liberty to the Stars and Stripes (2008), 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER28-ER29. (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
  - American Symbols: From Lady Liberty to the Stars and Stripes, Digital Documents and Photographs, 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.51 Gigabytes 47 computer files (Folder ER28)
  - American Symbols, a film by Pentagram, Digital Video Recording, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.211 Gigabytes Two computer files (Folder ER29)
  - The Fabric of Cultures: Fashion, Identity, Globalization (2008), 2006-2008; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER30-ER32. (Box 22, Folder 9-10)
  - The Fabric of Cultures: Fashion, Identity, Globalization, Digital Presentation, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.246 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER30)
  - The Fabric of Cultures: Fashion, Identity, Globalization, Digital Documents and Photographs, 2006; Archival Resource Key; 0.102 Gigabytes 65 computer files (Folder ER31)
  - Basha to Spun Steel, Digital Video Recording, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.413 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER32)
  - The Shape of Things: Paper Traditions and Transformations (2008-2009), 2007-2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER33-ER34. (Box 22, Folder 11-12)
  - Jennifer Falck Linssen, Digital Documents and Photographs, 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.19 Gigabytes 11 computer files (Folder ER33)
  - Robert Lang, Flapping Birds and Space Telescopes, Digital Video Recording, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.058 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER34)
  - Inside/Outside: Artist Environments (2009), 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1videodisc (DVD). Transfer not possible. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Warren MacKenzie: Legacy of an American Potter (2009), Archival Resource Key (Box 22)
    - Artists and Mailing Lists, 2002-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and Research, 2002-2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER35. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Warren Mackenzie Interview, Edited from Oral History Interview with Robert Silberman for Archives of American Art, Digital Audio Recording, 2002; Archival Resource Key; 0.179 Gigabytes 30 computer files (Folder ER35)
    - Installation, 2002-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Outreach and Public Programs, 2002-2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER36. (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Warren MacKenzie at the Trax Gallery, a film by Blar Gershkow, Digital Video Recording, 2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.777 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER36)
    - Touring Program Information, 2002-2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, ER37-ER38. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Legacy of an American Potter, Exhibition at Rochester Art Center, Digital Document, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.289 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER37)
    - Warren MacKenzie, Digital Documents, Photographs, and Audio Recordings, 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.245 Gigabytes 84 computer files (Folder ER38)
  - Open Source Embroidery (2009-2010), Archival Resource Key (Box 23)
    - Artists, Budget, Communication, 2009-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Equipment and Exhibition Proposal, 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Installation, Loan Forms, Outreach, 2007-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Press Material, 2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER39. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Patricia Polese, Digital Photographs and Documents, 2005-2009; Archival Resource Key; 0.052 Gigabytes 54 computer files (Folder ER39)
    - Public Programs and Transportation, 2009-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Clare Rojas: We They, We They (2010), Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER40. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Clare Rojas: We They, We They, Digital Photographs, 2010; Archival Resource Key; 0.02 Gigabytes 24 computer files (Folder ER40)
  - Rhythm and Hues: Cloth and Culture of Mali (2010), 2010-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Volver: Mexican Folk Art Into Play (2010-2011), Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER41. (Box 23, Folder 8-10)
  - Looped Surveillance Video, A. Miguelez and Jesica James (2010), Digital Video Recording, 2019; Archival Resource Key; 0.227 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER41)
  - E is for Everyone: Celebrating Sister Corita (2011), Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER42-ER45. (Box 23, Folder 11-13)
  - This E is for the Eames / Corita Connection, Films by Charles and Ray Eames, (1956-1968), Digital Video Recording, 2019; Archival Resource Key; 0.227 Gigabytes One computer file (Partial transfer only.) (Folder ER42)
    Film included: Parade (1952)
  - Sister Corita at Greative Growth (2011), Digital Video Recording, 2019; Archival Resource Key; 0.227 Gigabytes One computer file (Partial transfer only.) (Folder ER43)
  - Primary Colors, The Story of Corita, Film by Jeffrey Hayden (1991), Digital Video Recording, 2019; Archival Resource Key; 0.227 Gigabytes One computer file (Partial transfer only.) (Folder ER44)
  - Become a Microscope, 90 Statements on Sister Corita, a film by Aaron Rose (2008), Digital Video Recording, 2019; Archival Resource Key; 0.227 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER45)
    Partial transfer only.
  - Fiber Futures: Japan's Textile Pioneers (2011), 2011-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER46. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Fiber Futures: Japan's Textile Pioneers, Digital Documents, 2011; Archival Resource Key; 0.002 Gigabytes Five computer files (Folder ER46)
  - Wrapping Traditions: Korean Textiles Now (2011), 2009-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
  - Fiat Lux: Randy Colosky New Works (2011-2012), Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Only Birds Sing the Music of Heaven in this World (2012), Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER47-ER49. (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Interview of John Cerney, Digital Video Recording, 2012; Archival Resource Key; 0.106 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER47)
  - Interview of Chris Bunn and Jose Lepe Lepe, Digital Video Recording, 2012; Archival Resource Key; 0.155 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER48)